[♪ opening theme song playing]
[GONZO] We can all eat
together in here.
My goodness.
The great hall has
certainly seen better days.
You want me to fix it?
If you would.
[HAGURE] Oof. This'll be one
heck of a job.
What?
[HAGURE] Mm...
[RIGHT] Uh?
-It vanished.
-A clean slate.
[HAGURE] Mm...
[all gasp]
Glad that's settled,
'cause I'm starting to get
real hungry.
It's like the floor
was never damaged.
[DERA] What?
How does it work?
-Let me introduce my daemons.
-[BOTH] Huh?
Meet Black and White.
On my left shoulder,
I've got Whiteout.
And Ink is on the right.
If I wanna fix something,
Whiteout erases for me.
Then Ink draws in new stuff.
You have to be imaginative
and observant to use them.
That's why an artist
is the perfect person
to command these daemons.
You're an artist?
I work as a mangaka.
I'm Hikaru Hagure!
[both spit]
Oh, and please don't mind
the spitting.
Believe it or not, that's how
these two show affection.
[YURU] "Mangaka?"
What's that mean?
Huh? I know you!
They made a bunch of movies
outta the stories you published.
I've seen them!
Thanks for your support!
I'm lucky to make a good living
as an artist.
Hagure is just
a pen name, though.
My real name is actually
Hikaru Kagemori.
A pen name?
An alias.
[HAGURE] Our family's got
a ruthless reputation,
so I figured it was smart
to use a pseudonym.
You know,
to avoid controversy.
So the great mangaka's
a Kagemori, too?
To be specific,
the three of us are brothers.
I'm the oldest of the bunch.
I'm the middle child.
And I'm the kid brother,
of course.
Really? Weird.
Seriously?
You're the youngest one?
The baby.
Let me explain.
You're probably wondering
why we don't really look
anything alike. [laughs]
Three different moms.
As the eldest,
Hagure will one day
be the head of our clan.
So you'd be wise to stay
in his good graces.
No way, dude!
I am not cut out to lead
a sketchy clan like this.
All I want is a peaceful life
where I get to draw cute little
manga stories until I die.
I still have a decent
set of morals, you know.
Unlike you guys.
I kinda thought
that the more screwed up
the creator was,
the more interesting
their stories turned out.
You're stereotyping.
[DERA] Hm... Mr. Mangaka,
you may have
repaired everything,
but your fixes
are in monochrome.
Are you really sure
this is safe?
There's nothing to worry about.
The surrounding colors
will eventually bleed into it.
You won't be able
to tell the difference.
Ugh... The pillar details
are way off, though.
I made it look too clean.
The edges are sharp,
but given the building's age,
they should've been
smoothed over by time and touch.
What an absolute
amateur mistake.
[grunts] And the floor's wrong!
The tatami mats have seen
a ton of foot traffic
over the years
and should look way more
beaten up than this!
These are practically brand new!
Ah, man. What was I thinking?
I'm redoing this immediately!
[JIN]
Can we eat breakfast first?
[SERVANT] Thank you all
for your patience.
Breakfast is served.
Please, sit wherever you'd like.
Let's keep this casual.
We're an upstart clan,
so we're not overly concerned
with traditions
or things like seating order
and etiquette at the moment.
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two!
-[TSUGAI 2] Three, four!
Please sit.
Oh, thank you.
[TSUGAI 3]
Left, right, left, right.
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two!
-[TSUGAI 2] Three, four!
What's this? You're preparing
seats for us as well?
You do realize we don't consume
human food.
Sure, but you're
still our guests.
And we treat
all of our guests equally.
So, you knew
Mr. Big Brother was here.
You care to tell us how?
Nah, it's a secret.
-Mmm.
-[JIN] Curious.
The mansion was attacked
by multiple daemons last night.
I assume that Higashi Village
sent them to kill us.
[DERA] Uh, don't ask me.
[HAGURE] Aw, man.
So much for having
a lighthearted breakfast.
I didn't order an attack
on Kagemori headquarters,
if that's what you're implying.
[JIN] It happened
right after Yuru arrived.
Don't you think
that timing is suspicious?
Mm? Whoa!
[ASA] My brother is eating
in front of me.
And from what I understand,
members of the Tadera clan
can slip through barriers.
Our own barriers, sure.
Not ones that belong
to other people.
[ASA] Oh, my gosh, my brother
is drinking miso soup.
-That's good!
-More importantly, Asa.
Have the Kagemoris been
mistreating you?
You can save your concern.
They've fed me well
and treated me with kindness
ever since I came to them.
This manor's a fortress.
I'm safe from assassin attacks
as long as I remain
on the grounds.
Though last night's raid
was obviously an exception.
And take one step
outside the gates,
and enemies are all over you.
[SAKURAZAWA] I don't approve
of her leaving the manor,
but when our infirmary
is insufficient,
she's forced to visit
outside clinics for treatment.
Her safety and security
are always an issue
whenever that happens.
That's how
the Higashi Village assassins
managed to get me.
They timed their attack
for when I was recovering
at the hospital.
Whoa, recovering?
You must've been seriously sick.
[ASA] Thanks to you.
The stress of constantly
being targeted
by Higashi Village agents
gave me a gastric ulcer,
meaning my stomach felt like
I'd swallowed battery acid.
[DERA] Hey,
don't look at me like that.
I wasn't the one
giving the orders.
[ASA] Also, hospitals are full
of innocent bystanders,
so it's a real pain for everyone
when assassins show up.
Stop sending them.
I told you,
it's not my fault, I swear.
Please blame
the extremists instead.
For what it's worth, I'm sorry
they've caused problems.
[Dera gasps]
Hey, hold on.
You must have insurance!
Hospitals will
bleed you dry without it.
So, how did you become
an official citizen?
I gotta figure something out
for Yuru.
I haven't been able to register
with the government yet.
[DERA] Eesh.
That must be tough.
It should have been simple,
since my mother is from here.
In theory, all I needed to do
was register as her daughter.
But then somebody attacked her
and she and my father vanished,
leaving no trace.
What?
You mean your parents
are missing?
So she says.
Oh, boy. Look, kid,
I know I'm technically
on Higashi Village's side,
but I promise this is the first
I've heard about
them disappearing.
At the very least,
I doubt anyone that I know
in the community
would be behind
whatever happened to them.
And you really
expect us to take you,
an enemy agent, at your word?
While it's my duty
to kill anybody
who intrudes on our territory,
I don't attack people
for no reason.
And I don't agree with
any of the radicals who do.
I'm not even armed!
I showed up on your doorstep
in good faith
looking for Yuru, not a fight.
Have you considered that maybe
Kagemori extremists
are the ones to blame?
I've heard your clan
isn't a monolith, either.
You've got your own bad apples.
The twins have been reunited.
I'm wondering,
"What is it you plan
to do with them?"
[Gonzo exhales]
[GONZO] Each time
twins like you are born,
the world is thrown into chaos.
Humanity is better off
without Break or Seal.
It would be best for everyone
if Asa and Yuru
were the final set of twins,
and their backwards village
were simply destroyed
once and for all.
It's a wretched place
filled with wretched people,
consumed by outdated values
and dreams of conquering
the rest of us.
They are too great a threat.
And since we share their blood,
it's our responsibility
to make sure
they're taken care of.
[ASUMA] I disagree, Father.
I believe that those chosen
to wield great power
should use their gifts
to govern the world
and ensure peace.
They were granted
their abilities by the gods,
were they not?
The onus is on them
to use it wisely.
I'm guessing you think
your clan is best suited
to control that power.
[ASUMA] Yes. The village
that produces Break and Seal
should be allowed to live on.
We mustn't reject
their very existence.
That said,
they need to be controlled
by suitable overseers.
Like our organization.
Left and Right?
Go on.
Earlier, I asked if the twins
were cursed
to throw the world into chaos.
You denied it
without hesitation.
You said it's those
who wish to abuse the power
for their own ends who wind up
causing problems, yes?
You were certain.
And so quick to tell me
we weren't at fault.
Took a massive weight
off my shoulders.
You made me feel like it's
all right for me to just live.
So thank you.
I appreciate the meal.
This girl...
She apologizes for everything.
I'm not about to forgive her
for what she did to the village,
but I've seen her apologizing
for things
that aren't her fault.
Who convinced her
she needs to live
with her shame
hanging around her neck?
Who convinced her that
every little thing is her fault?
Why should we be forced
to live in secret?
Just because we're the twins
in some ancient prophecy?
Why should anybody but us
get to say
how we live our lives?
[Asa gasps softly]
You had agreed your clan
isn't a monolith, either.
I'm sure the extremists
will hear this,
and that doesn't bother me
one bit.
And Dera...
You can report this
to Higashi, too.
Because if no one wants
to give me any peace,
fine! I'm not gonna live
my life on the run!
And I've got
no reason to hide!
I don't care if you're
from Higashi or the Kagemoris.
I'm not afraid.
If you want my head,
come and get it!
Just know...
After I beat them
black and blue,
I'll squeeze them for
all the information they've got.
Whoa. Slow down, there.
How dare you be such an idiot!
[ASA] How dare you be
such an idiot!
[Yuru stutters]
[Yuru grunts]
Hey, hold on!
Who are you calling an idiot?
[ASA] "No reason to hide?"
That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard!
You're lucky!
You can say stuff like that
because you don't know
what it's like being hounded
by assassins night and day
for your whole life.
But I don't want you to suffer
like I have all these years!
So run! Or lay low somewhere!
Don't throw your life away!
What's this kid's deal?
Is he the type who only knows
"go big or go home?"
I'd say so.
[ASA] You two, help me get it
through his thick skull... Uh?
Ah, but as his daemons,
we must always do
as our master says, lass!
Should trouble befall us,
we've no choice but to fight!
You don't seem too broken up
about that.
I really don't see the problem.
You've been dealing with this
alone for way too long.
Why don't you
let your big brother
take some of the heat off you
for a change?
You're with him?
We have the most kind-hearted
of masters, do we not?
Hold on!
Obviously, I know
that his heart is kind.
I get it.
[Dera breathes uneasily]
[Yuru groans softly]
Tell me, Yuru.
Would you not consider joining
the Kagemoris
and coming to live with us?
You'll be safer here.
And we'll make sure
you're comfortable.
You'll want for nothing
under our roof. So?
-Not a chance.
-[GONZO] That was quick.
Of course.
You called Higashi and all
of its people wretched before.
But that's where
I was born and raised.
Those are my friends.
I respect that you have
your own way of thinking,
but just because I respect it
doesn't mean I accept it.
I can't see eye to eye
with someone
who did that to my home.
I know you're searching
for my parents,
and I'm grateful.
You look out for your own,
like you should.
I'll do the same, my way.
And for now, that means
working together with Dera.
[sighs]
I'm with your sister, frankly.
My life would be way easier
if you could try laying low.
But for the moment at least,
I'm the kid's guardian.
And that means supporting
whatever way he wants to live
and making sure he stays safe.
You mind if we scram?
About time we go.
But thanks
for all the hospitality.
[GONZO] Hm.
Hey, Left and Right...
Mr. Dera...
[Yuru gasps softly]
[ASA] I'm counting on you.
Please take care of my brother.
Of course, lass.
[LEFT] Mm-hmm.
Well, I'll try.
♪
I'm not able to walk you
any farther than here.
That's where the barrier ends.
If I take one step outside,
I'm liable to being attacked
by those who want Break.
[chuckles] Please be careful
out there, Yuru.
[YURU] So that's how it is.
She's trapped
inside these gates.
In the end,
the only difference
between the manor
and that cell is the size.
-Oh, yeah. I almost forgot.
-[YURU] Hm?
There's something
I wanna show you.
Look here.
[YURU] Huh?
What? That looks exactly
like our parents!
It's the last thing
I have of them
before they went missing.
[YURU] But what is it?
A painting?
[ASA] Uh, kind of like
a super realistic one,
I suppose?
Let me show you how it works.
Look up here.
-[phone camera clicks]
-[Yuru stammers]
[Yuru screams]
[ASA] This technology
perfectly preserves
a moment in time
to look back on later.
I do not understand this at all,
but it's one of the
coolest things
I've seen
in the world down here!
[ASA] Perfect.
I took advantage
of the situation
to get a keepsake of him!
A marvel!
We humbly request to be
in a preserved image
with our master as well!
I'm sorry to say it...
[phone camera clicks]
...but daemons don't usually
appear in photos.
You're like spirits.
Elusive and all.
They can be seen
on rare occasions
if the lighting and timing
manage to line up just right.
Ghost shows on TV
live for that stuff.
-[YURU] Asa...
-[ASA] Uh?
If you don't mind,
could I take a look again?
[ASA] Hm.
[Yuru chuckles] Their clothes
are from down here.
It's the first I've seen them
in ten years.
They look strange.
It isn't bad at all.
I wonder where they are
and how they're doing.
They are alive and healthy.
I'm positive.
I'll have this printed
and send it to you.
So I can keep it?
Although, I'll need
to get your address for that.
Where are you living these days?
What's that place called again?
Hang on, I know.
It was Guntama!
Say what, now?
This sucks.
I failed to take advantage
of the situation
to get my brother's address.
Hey, Dera...
I would give my address
to the Kagemoris,
but I'd rather not die
in my sleep.
What if we receive information
regarding his parents?
It'd be nice to reach out.
We won't ask for your address.
But maybe an email,
or your number?
Yeah, hell no.
You think I don't know
how easy it is
to doxx someone off
any random piece of info
-you might have?
-[Jin grunts]
I'll grant you,
it would be nice to have a way
to contact each other
if we ever need to.
Carrier pigeons?
Walky-talkies?
Encrypted notes
at Shinjuku Station?
Smoke signals!
[ALL] That's in violation
of fire laws.
[JIN] Oh, well. Come here
if you need anything.
Sending me to a girls' bar?
It's one of the businesses
run by the Kagemoris.
Just drop my name there
if you have a message for us.
They should pass it along.
That will be
our point of contact.
[DERA] Hmm...
That sounds good to me!
[JIN] He's clearly gonna
go there and drink on my tab.
[DERA] Anyway,
thanks for looking
for the twins' parents.
And thanks for
the lovely breakfast, too.
Before you go...
They were heartbroken that day.
Mom and Dad were inconsolable
when they realized they couldn't
get you off the mountain.
They did try, but Granny Yamaha
stopped them.
It was all they could do
to escape that place
with even one of their children.
They wanted us
to leave as a family.
So don't think for a second
they were all right after
having to leave you behind!
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[YURU] This trip was worth it,
if only just to hear that.
[Asa sniffles]
[YURU] Later.
[Jin gasps]
♪
[ASA] Listen, brother.
Take care of yourself.
Till next time.
[Yuru grunts, pants]
[DERA] Uh... Hey, Yuru?
[YURU] I messed up!
She caught me off guard!
If she were a bear,
I would be dead!
Are you for real, kid?
There's no doubt now.
That's her. That's Asa.
-[ASA] Listen...
-[YURU] Uh?
Brother, take care of yourself.
[Asa chuckles]
[Yuru cries]
That was her. That's my sister.
A little bigger,
but beyond a shadow of a doubt,
that was my real sister.
Why's it like this?
Damn it.
[birds chirping]
Jin, if you're thinking of
putting a tail on 'em, drop it.
Trust is imperative.
Yes, it is.
[GONZO] How troubling.
He commands the Divine Guardians
Left and Right,
which are meant to be held
by a third party
to check Break and Seal.
But instead, that check is gone.
And the inheritor of Seal
holds far more power
than expected
or was ever intended.
If something happens
to young Yuru,
there will be no one
to stop them.
What would happen after that?
Even I couldn't tell.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[Right yells, laughs]
[DERA]
Think they're Kagemori guys?
[YURU] We're being followed.
[GONZO] I'll just work you until
you wish you were dead!